[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 84, "question": "Any regrets at your end that you did that?", "question_tokens": ["Any", "regrets", "at", "your", "end", "that", "you", "did", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 85, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Clinton"]}, "docId": "120928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 93, "question": "I'm sorry, say that again, Piers?", "question_tokens": ["I", "'m", "sorry", ",", "say", "that", "again", ",", "Piers", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "IN", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 94, "answer": "I said I've sat down this week with President Clinton, with President Ahmadinejad --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "said", "I", "'ve", "sat", "down", "this", "week", "with", "President", "Clinton", ",", "with", "President", "Ahmadinejad", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 98, "question": "Couldn't the president have found time to have met some of them or maybe even come on my show and met them?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "n't", "the", "president", "have", "found", "time", "to", "have", "met", "some", "of", "them", "or", "maybe", "even", "come", "on", "my", "show", "and", "met", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 99, "answer": "Well, as I said, the president always makes time for world leaders.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "as", "I", "said", ",", "the", "president", "always", "makes", "time", "for", "world", "leaders", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Mitt Romney"]}, "docId": "120928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 124, "question": "I'd rather be the underdog on that first debate, wouldn't you?", "question_tokens": ["I", "'d", "rather", "be", "the", "underdog", "on", "that", "first", "debate", ",", "would", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 125, "answer": "Well, that's great advice for Mitt Romney.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "'s", "great", "advice", "for", "Mitt", "Romney", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}, "docId": "120928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 185, "question": "What does Mitt Romney do if Barack Obama does that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "Mitt", "Romney", "do", "if", "Barack", "Obama", "does", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 186, "answer": "Well, Mitt Romney has said a couple things since, piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Mitt", "Romney", "has", "said", "a", "couple", "things", "since", ",", "piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney", "Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "."], "qSentId": 246, "question": "Have you done that yet?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "done", "that", "yet", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 247, "answer": "I'm going to.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "going", "to", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "120928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 248, "question": "You will be seeing Netanyahu this week?", "question_tokens": ["You", "will", "be", "seeing", "Netanyahu", "this", "week", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "NNP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 249, "answer": "I generally see the prime minister when he's in the United States.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "generally", "see", "the", "prime", "minister", "when", "he", "'s", "in", "the", "United", "States", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 252, "question": "How will he react to this?", "question_tokens": ["How", "will", "he", "react", "to", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 253, "answer": "Well, I hope he will react positively.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "hope", "he", "will", "react", "positively", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 274, "question": "What would happen if the Israelis say you know what, we're not sensing anyone's with us, we're going on our own here, we're gong to defend ourselves, we're going to launch a strike now against these nuclear sites in Iran -- if they do that, what does a Romney administration do?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "happen", "if", "the", "Israelis", "say", "you", "know", "what", ",", "we", "'re", "not", "sensing", "anyone", "'s", "with", "us", ",", "we", "'re", "going", "on", "our", "own", "here", ",", "we", "'re", "gong", "to", "defend", "ourselves", ",", "we", "'re", "going", "to", "launch", "a", "strike", "now", "against", "these", "nuclear", "sites", "in", "Iran", "--", "if", "they", "do", "that", ",", "what", "does", "a", "Romney", "administration", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "POS", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 275, "answer": "Well, first off, Piers, I would just contest one thing.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "off", ",", "Piers", ",", "I", "would", "just", "contest", "one", "thing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iran"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 300, "question": "Do you know how the conversation went with Mitt Romney?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "how", "the", "conversation", "went", "with", "Mitt", "Romney", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 301, "answer": "Well, it was -- obviously it was a one-on-one conversation.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "was", "--", "obviously", "it", "was", "a", "one-on-one", "conversation", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 323, "question": "Were you?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 324, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 334, "question": "How are you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 335, "answer": "Desperate to se you.", "answer_tokens": ["Desperate", "to", "se", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["tens of millions of dollars"]}, "docId": "120928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "NNS", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 338, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 339, "answer": "Because you have a spanking new stage, at vast expense which houses 250 people and you signed some absolutely gargantuan new deal worth tens and tens of millions of dollars.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "you", "have", "a", "spanking", "new", "stage", ",", "at", "vast", "expense", "which", "houses", "250", "people", "and", "you", "signed", "some", "absolutely", "gargantuan", "new", "deal", "worth", "tens", "and", "tens", "of", "millions", "of", "dollars", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "NNS", "MD", "VB", ",", "JJ", ",", "IN", "POS", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", ",", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 361, "question": "What do you make of the election race?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "the", "election", "race", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 362, "answer": "I don't -- I can't take it seriously enough to think that it's a threat but then people will say, oh, that's so silly for you to think, like --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "--", "I", "ca", "n't", "take", "it", "seriously", "enough", "to", "think", "that", "it", "'s", "a", "threat", "but", "then", "people", "will", "say", ",", "oh", ",", "that", "'s", "so", "silly", "for", "you", "to", "think", ",", "like", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 363, "question": "Will you vote?", "question_tokens": ["Will", "you", "vote", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 364, "answer": "Of course.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "course", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 418, "question": "You enjoyed that one, didn't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "enjoyed", "that", "one", ",", "did", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "CD", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 419, "answer": "Yes, I did.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 432, "question": "People bailing on you?", "question_tokens": ["People", "bailing", "on", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 433, "answer": "I never had anyone bail on me once they were in the studio.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "never", "had", "anyone", "bail", "on", "me", "once", "they", "were", "in", "the", "studio", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["P. Diddy"]}, "docId": "120928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 436, "question": "Anybody good?", "question_tokens": ["Anybody", "good", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 437, "answer": "Well, P. Diddy was 40 minutes late so I walked up to my office and I said, maybe it was 40, maybe it was like 30.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "P.", "Diddy", "was", "40", "minutes", "late", "so", "I", "walked", "up", "to", "my", "office", "and", "I", "said", ",", "maybe", "it", "was", "40", ",", "maybe", "it", "was", "like", "30", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 461, "question": "Why would I ever be talking about you in my spare time, though?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "would", "I", "ever", "be", "talking", "about", "you", "in", "my", "spare", "time", ",", "though", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 462, "answer": "That's what you were talking about.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "what", "you", "were", "talking", "about", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 466, "question": "How did that go?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "that", "go", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 467, "answer": "Well, it was fine.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "was", "fine", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Andre"]}, "docId": "120928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBZ", ",", "NNP"], "qSentId": 471, "question": "Which one?", "question_tokens": ["Which", "one", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 472, "answer": "The one with the strange name who runs hotels, Andre", "answer_tokens": ["The", "one", "with", "the", "strange", "name", "who", "runs", "hotels", ",", "Andre"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 475, "question": "No?", "question_tokens": ["No", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "aSentId": 476, "answer": "I don't think so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 478, "question": "You don't think so?", "question_tokens": ["You", "do", "n't", "think", "so", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 479, "answer": "I don't know about it if I have.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "about", "it", "if", "I", "have", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 501, "question": "Have you read \"Fifty Shades of Grey\"?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "read", "``", "Fifty", "Shades", "of", "Grey", "''", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 502, "answer": "I read the first seven chapters.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "read", "the", "first", "seven", "chapters", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 504, "question": "Was there anything in there you hadn't already done yourself?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "there", "anything", "in", "there", "you", "had", "n't", "already", "done", "yourself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "NN", "IN", "EX", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 505, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "CC", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 507, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 508, "answer": "I know you probably imagined differently and have several nights during the week when you go to bed.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "know", "you", "probably", "imagined", "differently", "and", "have", "several", "nights", "during", "the", "week", "when", "you", "go", "to", "bed", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 511, "question": "Are you?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 512, "answer": "You surprise me.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "surprise", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 517, "question": "No manacles?", "question_tokens": ["No", "manacles", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 518, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 522, "question": "Did you read the entire trilogy?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "read", "the", "entire", "trilogy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 523, "answer": "It's unreadable.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "unreadable", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 529, "question": "Why would you read that?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "would", "you", "read", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 530, "answer": "Just out of pure curiosity.", "answer_tokens": ["Just", "out", "of", "pure", "curiosity", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 546, "question": "You think I'm going to book Jen?", "question_tokens": ["You", "think", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "book", "Jen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 547, "answer": "I see you as a surrogate booker.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "see", "you", "as", "a", "surrogate", "booker", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 551, "question": "At Jennifer's wedding?", "question_tokens": ["At", "Jennifer", "'s", "wedding", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 552, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jennifer"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 562, "question": "You think you will ever get married?", "question_tokens": ["You", "think", "you", "will", "ever", "get", "married", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 563, "answer": "You know what, I was thinking about that, actually.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", "what", ",", "I", "was", "thinking", "about", "that", ",", "actually", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 597, "question": "How are you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 598, "answer": "Great, thanks.", "answer_tokens": ["Great", ",", "thanks", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 599, "question": "How are you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 600, "answer": "I feel under pressure.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "feel", "under", "pressure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States of America"]}, "docId": "120928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 605, "question": "Let me ask you off the top, do you think, given the financial state of the country, that having somebody with Romney's business background and business brain is a good idea, or do you think that's not really necessary in a commander-in-chief, in a president?", "question_tokens": ["Let", "me", "ask", "you", "off", "the", "top", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "given", "the", "financial", "state", "of", "the", "country", ",", "that", "having", "somebody", "with", "Romney", "'s", "business", "background", "and", "business", "brain", "is", "a", "good", "idea", ",", "or", "do", "you", "think", "that", "'s", "not", "really", "necessary", "in", "a", "commander-in-chief", ",", "in", "a", "president", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "POS", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 606, "answer": "I think running the United States of America is like running an enormous corporation.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "running", "the", "United", "States", "of", "America", "is", "like", "running", "an", "enormous", "corporation", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 615, "question": "Do you think you could still do that today?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "you", "could", "still", "do", "that", "today", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 616, "answer": "No, I think a lot of people are doing that.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "think", "a", "lot", "of", "people", "are", "doing", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RBR", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":", "IN", "VBN", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 626, "question": "What's your view?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "your", "view", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 627, "answer": "I think he is much better off in a suit than -- than colored trousers or chino trousers.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "he", "is", "much", "better", "off", "in", "a", "suit", "than", "--", "than", "colored", "trousers", "or", "chino", "trousers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", ":", "NN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 640, "question": "Alarming orange jacket there from Mr. Romney?", "question_tokens": ["Alarming", "orange", "jacket", "there", "from", "Mr.", "Romney", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "NN", "NN", "EX", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 641, "answer": "I think they are trying to sort of like -- sort of like the normal guys next door.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "they", "are", "trying", "to", "sort", "of", "like", "--", "sort", "of", "like", "the", "normal", "guys", "next", "door", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 662, "question": "Why is this such a cause dear to you, Tommy?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "is", "this", "such", "a", "cause", "dear", "to", "you", ",", "Tommy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 663, "answer": "My family has been affected by autism.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "family", "has", "been", "affected", "by", "autism", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Tommy"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120928pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":"], "qSentId": 697, "question": "How do you write your father's name?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "write", "your", "father", "'s", "name", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 698, "answer": "B-A-S --", "answer_tokens": ["B-A-S", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]